Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection, 1900-2004 and undated, bulk 1965-1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Mounted Advertisements Series, circa 1919-1998 and undated (Box OV8)
  - Canada (Box MAP3)
    - General (Box MAP3)
      - Toshiba, 1989 (Box MCA1)
      - Wardair Canada, 1988-1989 (Box MCA1)
  - Europe (Box MCA1)
    - General (Box MCA1)
      - Adams--Chiclets, 1989 (Box MEU1)
      - Amoreiras Shopping Center, undated (Box MEU1)
      - Bacardi Rum, 1988 (Box MEU1)
      - Blå Mocca coffee, undated (Box MEU1)
      - British Telecom, undated (Box MEU1)
      - Campari, 1988 (Box MEU1)
      - Cavit Trentino, 1987 (Box MEU1)
      - Coats thread, 1988 (Box MEU1)
      - Credito Agricola/Rural Seguros, undated (Box MEU1)
      - Dadak Coffee, circa 1998 (Box MEU1)
      - Danske Kaffe, 1988 (Box MEU1)
      - De Vere Hotels, 1988-1989 (Box MEU1)
      - DeBeers, 1988 and undated (Box MEU1)
      - Denim Eau de Toilette, 1989 (Box MEU1)
      - Diners' Club, 1988 (Box MEU1)
      - Dos Equis, 1988 (Box MEU1)
      - Eastman Kodak, 1989 (Box MEU2)
      - Elida face cream, 1989 (Box MEU2)
      - Esso, undated (Box MEU2)
      - Fini da Modena pasta, undated (Box MEU2)
      - Fleurop flower service, 1989 (Box MEU2)
      - Ford, 1960-1988 (Box MEU2)
      - German tourism, 1989 (Box MEU2)
      - Greenalls beer, 1988 (Box MEU2)
      - Hero Delicia preserves, 1989 (Box MEU2)
      - Jacobs coffee, undated (Box MEU2)
      - Johnny Walker, 1988 (Box MEU2)
      - Kellogg's, 1960s (Box MEU2)
      - Kenco coffee, undated (Box MEU2)
      - Kraft, 1989 (Box MEU3)
      - Lever--Coral detergent, 1988-1989 (Box MEU3)
      - Lever--Lux, undated (Box MEU3)
      - Médis health plan, undated (Box MEU3)
      - Nicola coffee, undated (Box MEU3)
      - Paddington & Co., 1986 (Box MEU3)
      - Philips, 1988-1989 (Box MEU3)
      - Pilkington--Reactolite Rapide/Sprint eyewear, 1988 (Box MEU3)
      - Pola, undated (Box MEU3)
      - R.J. Reynolds--Winston, 1988-1989 (Box MEU4)
      - Sharp electronics, 1989 (Box MEU4)
      - Technics, 1989 (Box MEU4)
      - Warner-Lambert--Benylin, 1989 (Box MEU4)
      - Warrington-Runcorn, 1988 (Box MEU4)
      - Wisla Vodka, undated (Box MEU4)
      - Yomi yogurt drink, 1988 (Box MEU4)
    - Madrid Office (Box MEU4)
      - Baguin S.A., 1988 (Box MEU5)
      - DeBeers, undated (Box MEU5)
      - Ford, 1984 (Box MEU5)
      - Futuro magazine, 1989 (Box MEU5)
      - Kraft--Ligeresa, undated (Box MEU5)
      - Kraft--Philadelphia cream cheese, undated (Box MEU5)
      - Kraft--Tang, undated (Box MEU5)
      - Nescafe, 1987 (Box MEU5)
      - R.J. Reynolds--Winston, 1988-1989 (Box MEU5)
    - Paris Office (Box MEU5)
      - Citior, undated (Box MEU6)
      - Disney Channel, 1997 (Box MEU6)
      - Ford, 1986 (Box MEU6)
      - Guerlain, circa 1990 (Box MEU6)
      - La Ville du Puy, undated (Box MEU6)
      - Maubousson, undated (Box MEU6)
      - Mazda, 1997 (Box MEU6)
      - R.J. Reynolds--Winston, undated (Box MEU6)
  - Latin America (Box MEU6)
    - General (Box MEU6)
      - AT&T, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Chispas, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - DeBeers, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Don Q, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Dos Equis, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Ford, 1961-1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Frito-Lay, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Halston, 1988 (Box MLA1)
      - Warner-Lambert (Lubriderm), 1989 (Box MLA2)
      - Modelo (Betsy Clark), 1988 (Box MLA2)
      - Tiempo Oster, 1989 (Box MLA2)
      - Samoa footwear, 1988 (Box MLA2)
      - Mastercard, 1988 (Box MLA2)
      - Lever Brothers (Lux), 1988 (Box MLA2)
      - Rolex, 1990 (Box MLA2)
      - Pisco Control, 1990 (Box MLA2)
      - Pepsi-Cola, undated (Box MLA2)
      - Lanas Cisne, 1990 (Box MLA2)
      - IBM, 1990 (Box MLA2)
      - Kraft, undated (Box MLA2)